sweetandsavorymeals.com 2019-06-27

# Privacy Policy - Sweet and Savory Meals

**Privacy Policy**

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.sweetandsavorymeals.com and Peas and Peonies LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Peas and Peonies LLC include www.sweetandsavorymeals.com. The Peas and Peonies LLC website is a Travel, Food & Recipes Blog site. By using the Peas and Peonies LLC website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

 **Collection of your Personal Information**

Peas and Peonies LLC may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

  * Name
  * E-mail Address

Peas and Peonies LLC may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your:

  * Age
  * Gender

We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Peas and Peonies LLC’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Peas and Peonies LLC encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Peas and Peonies LLC so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Peas and Peonies LLC is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Peas and Peonies LLC website.

 **Email Addresses**

We may collect your email address, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us. This may occur, for example, if you sign up to receive an email newsletter, or enter a promotion. If you have provided your email address to us, we promise to use it only for the purposes for which it is provided. We will not use your email address to contact you for unrelated reasons. We will not share your email address with any third parties. If you are a resident of a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), we do not wish to receive your email address, and will delete it you have provided it inadvertently.

 **Use of your Personal Information**

Peas and Peonies LLC collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Peas and Peonies LLC may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Peas and Peonies LLC and its affiliates. Peas and Peonies LLC may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Peas and Peonies LLC does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Peas and Peonies LLC may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Peas and Peonies LLC, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Peas and Peonies LLC may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Peas and Peonies LLC, in order to determine what Peas and Peonies LLC services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Peas and Peonies LLC to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Peas and Peonies LLC will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Peas and Peonies LLC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Peas and Peonies LLC; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Peas and Peonies LLC, or the public.

 **Automatically Collected Information**

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Peas and Peonies LLC. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Peas and Peonies LLC website.

 **Use of Cookies**

The Peas and Peonies LLC website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Peas and Peonies LLC pages, or register with Peas and Peonies LLC site or services, a cookie helps Peas and Peonies LLC to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Peas and Peonies LLC website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Peas and Peonies LLC features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Peas and Peonies LLC services or websites you visit.

 **Security of your Personal Information**

Peas and Peonies LLC secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Peas and Peonies LLC uses the following methods for this purpose:

  * SSL Protocol

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

 **Children Under Thirteen**

Peas and Peonies LLC does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

 **Advertising Privacy Statement**

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third-party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

 **For European Economic Area Residents**

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact AdThrive at info@adthrive.com. If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

 **Additional Rights of EEA (European Economic Area) Residents**

If you are a resident of a country in the EEA, you have the rights, among others, to:

(i) access your personal data

(ii) ensure the accuracy of your personal data

(iii) the right to have us delete your personal data

(iv) the right to restrict further processing of your personal data, and

(v) the right to complain to a supervisory authority in your country of residence in the event that data is misused

If you believe that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement.

You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us addressed to the following:

Peas and Peonies LLC

Attn: Catalina Castravet

123 Town Square Place Suite 178

Jersey City, NJ 07310

 **Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Peas and Peonies LLC by contacting us here:

Web page: [Contact](https://sweetandsavorymeals.com/contact/)

 **Changes to this Statement**

Peas and Peonies LLC will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Peas and Peonies LLC encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Peas and Peonies LLC is protecting your information.

 **Contact Information**

Peas and Peonies LLC welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Peas and Peonies LLC has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Peas and Peonies LLC at:

Peas and Peonies LLC

Attn: Catalina Castravet

123 Town Square Place Suite 178

Jersey City, NJ 07310

Email Address:

peasandpeonies@gmail.com

_________________

 **USING MY CONTENT**

If you would like to use one of my recipes or any of the pictures on my site, please give the proper credit to me. This can be done by linking back to my site. If you do use one of my recipes, please link back to the page where you found the recipe.

 **DISCLOSURE**

If a post is sponsored I will disclose this to my readers. The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made in this blog. All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third party ad network. Those advertisements will be identified as paid advertisements.

I am not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely my own opinions. I will only endorse products or services that I believe, based on my expertise and experience with the product or services. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

 **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at my discretion.

_________________

Effective as of May 25th, 2018
